Good.
The last shot was good.
I like this part.
Your dad told me
that Yudong
is a great choice.
You'll have
a better future there.
So you all think
it's a better choice?
It's not just our opinion.
The facts are there for all to see.
I can't deny that.
Coach Su,
you mentioned before
that your mom secretly signed you up
for the internship in Yibei.
How long did it take you
to realize it was the right choice?
Honestly,
the truth is,
I still don't know
if that was
the right choice.
There are so many paths in life.
How would you know
if it's right or wrong
until you reach the end?
Besides, many things
don't have absolute right or wrong.
As the saying goes, fortune and misfortune come hand in hand.
So I can't answer
your question.
If so,
how can we weigh the pros and cons?
You have to
follow your heart.
I might
want to
go back to Yibei.
What about you?
I don't know.
But I think
I'll just keep moving forward for now.
Morning, Dad.
Handsome.
Let's go.
Dad,
can I go by myself today?
By yourself?
Yes.
Why?
This is my own choice.
I want to face it myself.
Don't worry.
I won't do anything reckless.
If you're really worried,
you can call me the whole time.
That's not necessary.
I trust you.
Go by yourself.
Okay.
By the way, Dad,
I've put my reading notes on the table.
You can read them after I leave.
Call me if you need anything.
Goodbye, Dad.
Good luck.
Sir,
Yudong Middle School, please.
Okay.
[Dad,]
[I'm sorry.]
[This isn't a reading note,]
but a letter to you.
Frankly,
I've been
worried about
transferring schools.
Mom says
this is growing up.
You taught me
how to handle problems,
but this time,
I don't know how to
plan and deal with it.
But I've been thinking,
just like you
always encourage me.
A few days ago,
Mom showed me a lot of
your stuff from before,
and told me
about your path of struggle.
This has made me understand you even more,
I know your expectations
for me.
And,
Dad,
I suddenly realized something.
You have been
with me,
educating me,
and guiding me.
It's your love for me,
but on the other hand,
I think you are also
healing your past self
in this way.
The self who started from the hometown,
who fought alone for many years
with gritted teeth.
Your great concern for my future,
I think,
is also a continuation of the unease
in those long years.
I don't know if I'm right.
Dad,
I want to tell you
that you don't have to worry anymore.
Now, open
the box on the desk.
I have something to show you.
This is from the basketball team.
They gave it to me.
Why did you turn off the computer?
We're not doing anything wrong.
Let's give him a surprise.
I'm afraid it will be exposed in advance.
But in this way,
I'm afraid he will misunderstand more.
Song,
how is it?
Give me some professional feedback.
Senior,
I'm really not very familiar
with this aspect.
Don't be so modest.
You've been learning basketball for so many years.
I'll leave it to you.
Think about it.
Okay.
When are you going to post
those videos we shot?
I made a QR code.
After he finishes reading the plan,
he can scan it to see the videos.
Impressive!
Keep watching.
Bro.
We were really mad at you before.
But after I made
a call to auntie,
I began to understand you.
So,
I don't want to hold grudges.
I made a video for you.
The training plan you saw
is our attempt to follow your example.
We all worked hard to complete it.
We wanted to tell you,
even if you transfer away,
we will continue your part
and keep working hard.
Gu Chenyang,
given how impressive we are,
you can rest assured to go far and soar high,
and achieve great success.
And,
I'll keep training.
Gu Chenyang,
I support your choice,
just like you supported me.
Sorry,
I won't take over as captain.
No matter where you are,
the captain of Yibei,
player No. 30,
will always be you.
So don't let us down
in Yudong.
Gu Chenyang,
I've finished writing
the story of the basketball club.
Please come back
to see my next play.
Gu Chenyang,
bye.
There are many people for the interview today.
Please wait a moment.
Get ready.
The last one is done.
I'll call you when it's your turn.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Cheng.
You're welcome.
Good luck.
One, two, good luck!
Dad,
you raised me
to be an excellent person.
And now,
I've also influenced
my teammates.
They are all very good people.
They won't lead me astray,
nor will they leave me.
Instead, they will move forward with me.
Just like you and your good brother.
Dad,
I've fixed it for you.
The parts are no longer produced.
It can't be fixed.
Is there no substitute?
No.
Fixing it
is harder than I thought.
The master said there was a component
that was out of print.
I found
the supplier
of this company online,
and followed the legal person information
to contact them.
After all that,
I finally found
a substitute for the component,
and fixed it.
You're something, young man.
You even found
a substitute for this discontinued part.
You're quite impressive.
I could do this
because of the methods
you taught me since childhood.
Decompose the problem,
find the breakthrough,
and persevere to the end.
Dad,
I always remember
what you taught me.
And these
are enough for me
to move forward in any situation.
I can mend my friendship
and keep pursuing my dream.
No matter in the past or the future.
So,
Dad,
can you believe me this time?
Let me create
my own miracle
in Yibei.
Your son and eternal partner,
Gu Chenyang.
Cheer up!
Coach Su,
please select your starting lineup.
Lineup, right?
Yes.
No, no.
My stomach hurts.
I need to use the bathroom.
Coach Su,
just sign it.
Or, student, you...
I'm just a student.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Gu Chenyang.
Please, have a seat.
Thank you all very much
for giving me this interview opportunity.
But in the end, I've decided...
Dad!
Sorry.
Sorry, everyone.
I just want to tell my son
one thing.
Thank you.
Yang,
I read your report.
It's very good.
Yidong or Yibei,
you choose.
Don't worry about me.
Dad,
the competition is about to start.
We'll be late.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Let's go.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Coach Cheng,
see you at the game.
Let's go.
Coach,
how much longer do you need?
The referee is waiting.
Just a moment.
Hold them off a bit longer.
Coach,
is this really going to work?
We have to try.
What if it works?
Sorry,
just a moment longer.
Oh, no.
I didn't bring my jersey.
Where did I put it?
I'll go get it.
No need.
Xie Yizhou?
Why are you here?
I made a bet with them.
If you came today,
I would give you back the jersey.
If you didn't,
they'd keep it as a souvenir.
Sorry,
but you need to give it back now.
It was meant for you.
Come on, sign it.
Don't waste time.
Coach,
I'm late.
Not at all.
Come on.
Yibei!
Victory!
Yibei, come on!
No. 5 High School, come on!
25 seconds left.
No. 5 High School is leading by two points
and has possession of the ball.
Meanwhile,
Yibei is
on the edge of the cliff.
Who will
be the biggest dark horse
in this year's league?
Let's find out.
Alright.
The ball is served.
It's passed the halfway line smoothly.
Trying to move the ball to the basket.
Chen Song
makes a crucial steal.
The ball is stolen.
They got the ball.
Yibei's small lineup today
is truly mind-boggling.
Can they create a miracle?
Okay.
The ball goes to Lin Qingyuan.
Lin Qingyuan makes
a beautiful back-elbow pass.
Gu Chenyang tries a three-pointer.
It's in.
The ball's in!
Gu Chenyang's nailed the game-winning shot!
69 to 68!
They did it!
Yibei Middle School pulled off the comeback!
They've truly made a miracle!
Let's congratulate
Yibei Middle School on the game-winning shot!